Countries worldwide
are battling
a discrete yet fierce information warfare.
Two countries are in a standoff.
Ostania in the east.
Westalis in the west.
Westalis launched Operation Strix
to find out the movements of
key figures in the Ostanian government,
who are plotting a war.
B-1 Agent Twilight,
in charge of the operation,
has successfully completed Phase One,
which was to create a family,
and enroll his daughter into
a prestigious school.
Father is a spy.
Mother is an assassin.
Daughter is a telepath.
The mission continues, as all three
hide their identities from each other.
To date, they've managed to secure
one of the eight Stellas that are
necessary to become an honor student.
The mission has now entered Phase Two,
which is to attend
the reception where the target,
Desmond, will appear.
ORIGINAL WORK BY TATSUYA ENDO
SERIALIZED ON SHUEISHA'S SHONEN JUMP PLUS
All right. Everything is ready.
Let's get started.
Onto further news.
Minister Brantz arrived at
Berlint Airport yesterday afternoon
with a delegation from Westalis.
They will try to arrange
a discussion between
the East and West at the summit
that begins tonight…
Are you okay?
Hey. Eat slowly.
Thanks for the food!
Father, Mother, hurry up!
-She's so restless.
-She can't help it.
Because today is the day…
MISSION:13
PROJECT APPLE
The dog goes bark, bark
Anya, you're in such a good mood.
Do dogs eat peanuts?
I heard it's best not to give them those.
What? Boo.
Let's give the doggie what he likes.
The reason for our outing today,
or rather the objective
of Operation Strix…
is the pet shop.
We're here.
It's because Anya said that she wanted
a dog as a reward for getting a Stella.
Until she gets eight Stellas
for me to attend the reception,
I must make sure to keep her motivated.
A reward! Reward! Bark, bark!
Welcome!
Well, what do you say?
All of them have received
hands-on practical training.
This shop is backed by the organization
and they sell military dogs.
I thought we might as well get a dog
that we can count on for security, but…
These dogs are cute, and look intelligent.
Right, Anya?
Oh no! That look on her face
means she really hates it!
Don't you have ones that are
smaller and cuter?
-Anya doesn't want them.
-I can ask a fellow breeder.
Yes, they look a bit scary.
Apparently, there's an adoption event
going on right now at the shelter.
Then we'll head over there.
A new mission?
Sorry. My stomach isn't feeling well,
so can you head over to the shelter
by the train station?
I'll look for a restroom.
Are you okay?
I think we should wait for you here.
Father shits for a really long time,
so we should head out first.
Is… Is that right? I understand.
Don't use such foul language.
Although that was a good save…
it's a little…
Wait a minute! You didn't tell me that
we were going to the Headquarters!
My family will get suspicious
if I take too long.
Make your complaints to your handler.
You were called for an emergency.
An assassination plot
against Minister Brantz?
They're probably plotting
against the summit tonight.
We believe the criminals are a group of
isolationist students
from Berlint University.
The Secret Police were keeping
an eye on them as well.
We caught one of them stalking around
the embassy, and he's being interrogated.
But he hasn't given any information
about his friends.
And… that's why I was called?
You're a dad and an agent.
Wearing two hats must be difficult.
Being a father is a part of my mission.
But is this what the world is coming to?
Young kids like this are becoming
terrorists now?
You'll never be able to make me talk!
I won't sell out my friends.
That's fine. We don't need you anymore.
We caught your leader.
Keith!
It's him!
He's the one that planned it all!
He persuaded us to join him!
-Believe me! It's not my fault!
-Hey Keith! What are you saying?
I'll tell you everything.
-Please let me go!
-Quiet! Keep walking!
That bastard! He's planning to frame me?
What a great friend.
Well, I don't care who the leader is.
All we care about is the person
who will give us the information.
Now, you will be taken to--
Wait! It's not me! He's the leader!
I'm not lying! He's the one
that came to us with the plans!
Let's hear all the details.
Keith planned everything.
It's a good thing
we found video footage of Keith.
It was almost impossible to be disguised
as Keith based on such short footage.
If that kid was a professional,
he would've seen through me.
There's also Kevin and Kim
from the Engineering Department.
That's everyone that I know of.
We used the warehouse
near the university as our hideout,
and the room above the bar on 11th Avenue.
What's the specific plan
for the assassination?
Dogs.
I don't know the exact number,
but a few dozen dogs will be strapped
with bombs,
and they're going to attack
during transit.
Bomb dogs?
This is not good. It's difficult to stop
dogs that have been trained.
I can't believe this.
Providing military training for one dog,
costs as much as a small missile.
I can hardly believe that college students
would have that kind of money.
Now we're seeing a possibility
of a far-right group
or a foreign country backing them.
As you already heard,
things have become complicated.
We must get a head start,
in order to stop this terrorist attack.
How about we cancel the summit?
That'll be impossible. It will make
the East's ruling party look bad.
Although it would please
the opposing party.
Leak this information to the ruling party.
They would want to avoid
any unnecessary problems.
Yes.
I'm sorry, but we'll need you
a little longer.
I understand.
The relationship between East and West
is on thin ice.
In addition to the outcome
of this assassination plot,
this information becoming public
could also put things at risk.
We will prevent this at all costs.
I'm going to go buy some coffee.
Wait here.
Be good, tail-waggers.
These dogs sure are smart.
Although they seem to be pretty old.
Careful.
Don't run. You'll fall.
Hey, stop!
-Hey, what are you doing?
-He's going to eat me!
-That signboard came crashing down!
-That was close!
Did you save me?
Thank you.
Sorry about my dog.
Don't go off on your own, idiot!
-What happened?
-He ran off on his own.
Is it really a good idea
to use these dogs?
It's too late to change our plans now.
We finished inspecting and marking
the area, so let's head back.
We don't want to get Keith mad.
That'll be troublesome.
So this is what an adoption event
looks like? It's a grand event!
I wonder why Loid didn't choose
to come here to begin with?
These doggies are small!
And cats!
And rabbits!
Don't run around Anya. You'll get lost!
Listen up.
You must not leave this doggie corner
on your own.
Understood.
That dachshund is so cute!
Look at those short legs!
They're cute even when
they're short-legged? Is Anya cute too?
Chihuahua! Pomeranian!
Breathe…
Are you looking for a dog?
Do you have a breed that's easy to raise?
Breathe…
What a big dog.
It's Anya's house.
What's wrong? Hurry up and walk!
What I saw right now… Did that image
come from that doggie's mind?
A toy poodle doesn't shed much,
so it's fairly easy to maintain.
Mother! I saw a dog that knows
about our house!
Hm? What are you talking about?
As for smaller dogs,
Shih Tzus are very gentle…
I'll take a quick look…
Is this a store?
Where is that doggie?
Doggie.
Who are you?
You better have not attracted
any attention.
No worries!
There was an adoption event,
so everyone had dogs.
The time has finally come.
If this plan using the bomb dogs succeeds,
the relation between the east and west
will undoubtedly come to an end.
In order to bring Ostania back
to its former glory,
we will have Minister Brantz
become a smoke signal
that announces the start of war.
We'll crush those arrogant pigs
in Westalis!
We'll crush them!
They're bad guys?
This house belongs to the bad guys!
Hey! What are you guys doing?
This kid was eavesdropping on you guys!
Are you serious? Who is that?
Wh… what should we do?
You're wondering what to do?
We obviously have to get rid of her.
Stop it, Keith! She's just a kid.
Our plan will be ruined
if she goes and tattles to her parents.
Kurt, cover her mouth.
-Whoa!
-Oh!
Doggie.
He's running around on his own again.
It seems like he's a defect.
You chose the wrong person to bark at!
I'll shut you up.
Huh?
That idiot.
Stop it. Don't waste your weapon on him.
But we have to shut him up.
Don't worry about that.
No one would think anything
of a barking dog today.
Anya! Where are you?
Excuse me! Have you seen a small child
with two little ornaments on her head?
I'm not sure.
I don't think I have.
She's not here.
She's nowhere in this hall.
Did she get eaten by a dog?
Calm down, Yor! That idea is impossible.
In that case, was she…
kidnapped?!
Cases of young women being kidnapped
and forced into marriage
are occurring frequently in Central Alian…
My, how scary!
-I'll make you my wife.
-Oh no!
What should I do?
Anya will be forced into marriage!
At a time like this
when Loid isn't with us!
What should I do?
What am I supposed to do?
Loid, hurry up and come back
from the bathroom!
We got nothing from the two
hideout locations the kid told us about.
How about you?
I got a lead.
Two white vans were rented
under the name of
one of the members, Kevin Knowles.
License plate is…
Good work. I'll have someone
look into it right away.
And as for the source of those dogs,
I'm starting to smell something fishy.
I'm sure you've heard of it.
Project Apple.
The former Ostanian government
conducted research
to create highly intelligent animals
for military use.
I'm aware of that.
It seems like they were repeatedly
conducting extreme experiments,
but the administration collapsed
and the research came to a stop.
The research was incomplete,
ending nowhere near their objective.
Yes. There were rumors that those dogs
and research subjects
were sold on the black market
instead of being destroyed.
Do you think that the terrorists got
their hands on them?
There's a possibility of that.
Although they're survivors of
a failed experiment
those dogs are still
rather intelligent,
and they received training as well.
Be careful.
We may come across
an unexpected situation.
Get away from that dog, little brat.
I promise to finish you off
without much pain.
A phone call?
Hey. You better hurry up, or I'll…
Man, that scared me.
Who's calling us at a time like this?
Hello?
What? Are you serious?
We're in trouble, Keith!
Some people raided two of our hideouts!
Was it the Secret Police?
Why? Did someone leak our information?
Kris has been missing
ever since this morning.
So I was prepared for the worst, but…
Good thing we changed location.
Don't panic, everyone!
We'll change to Plan B…
Hey! Where's the kid?
Huh? What?
Doggie, are you on my side?
More importantly, did you know
that the phone was going to ring?
You can see the future?
You're just like Anya.
You have supernatural powers.
Doggie, go inside that building.
We're going to have Mother save us!
No, don't go that way!
Go back!
Anya!
Damn it!
What have you bastards done?
-We were distracted by the phone…
-We have bigger fish to fry!
-Let's get on with our plan.
-Idiots! She saw us!
Come here, Kurt!
We'll take one of the dogs too!
We're going after them?
Take down the map on the wall.
We'll leave this hideout.
You guys scatter and meet up
at the spot we planned on.
Got it.
Hey, stop right now and let me off!
Someone help me!
Anya is being chased by bad guys!
What's going on? How cute.
Are they playing tag?
Doggie runs very fast.
It's so fast, and…
Exciting!
All right, Doggie,
let's outrun them
and go to the police station!
Anya and Doggie
will solve this case on our own,
and all will be well!
And I will become Starlight Anya
once again!
That saved us time.
We're back to where we started!
Turn around and go right!
I won't let you go.
Kill her. Quickly.
Sure.
Don't resent me for this.
I will not allow this.
You perverted kidnapper.
It's too early for marriage for Anya!
MISSION:14
DISARM THE TIME BOMB
Subtitle translation by: Lili Morita